Finding Aid for The Frick Collection Central Files, 1932-1936 TFC.0400.010
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Central Files, 1934
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] [3 folders], 1934 (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
    Topics covered include costs; air conditioning duct work; soundproofing; shoring and excavation conditions; wood molding moved from over door of Mrs. Frick's Boudoir to present Boucher Room; electrical work, conduits and windpipes for organ; and no smoking instructions issued to workmen.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Bills re Maintenance Account, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Bills and Requisitions, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Contains itemized list of subcontractors paid on each monthly bill, with work done penciled in next to each name.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Copies of Letters [8 folders], 1934 Jan.-Aug. (Box 11, Folder 14-21)
    Re increases or decreases in estimated costs, with explanations.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Copies of Letters [4 folders], 1934 Sep.-Dec. (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Estimates, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Twelve oversize documents removed - stored in Box A.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Memoranda to Job Office, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Progress Photographs, 1934 Jan.-Apr. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Seven views of The Collection and Library construction progress from 71st Street, and one from Fifth Avenue and 70th Street. Photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Statements of Estimated Cost Status, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Contains monthly reports of approved estimated cost status to date, with lists of extra items approved.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Statements of Expenditures and Commitments, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Oversize charts stored in Box B.
  - Eidlitz, Marc & Son [general contractors] - Watchmen Service, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Employees [RESTRICTED FILE], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Equipment for Library, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Equipment for Museum, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Expense Accounts (Frederick Mortimer Clapp), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Eisinger, L. W. [Clerk of the Works]
    Electrical Research Products Inc. - Oversize drawing on tracing paper of southeast and southwest corners of Enamels Room stored in Box B.
  - Fifth Avenue Association, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statements, 1931-1933 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Fire Extinguishers, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Flood Control, 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Re flooding in the sub-basement.
  - Floors, Care of, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Fresco, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Re Frick Art Reference Library Reading Room fresco by Nicholas Lochoff. Contains notes on materials and measurements.
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Contains letter of apology to Clapp from Library staff for sounding ungrateful and complaining about the imperfections in the new building. Photograph (two copies) of front of building, near completion, transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopy of photograph.
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Bills for Steam, Water and Electricity, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Manning, Ethelwyn [Librarian], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Frick Art Reference Library - Report on Construction of Old Library Building, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Contains report describing materials, finishes, furniture and mechanical details of each room and floor in the Library.
  - Frick, Mr. Childs [Trustee], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Contains letter re charge for the following salvage material from the Frick residence: plumbing fixtures, wrought iron fences and gates, carved stone in porte-cochere and court, and canvas ceiling from Mrs. Frick's bedroom.
  - Frick, Miss Helen C. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Contains correspondence, and summaries of conversations and meetings between Clapp and Miss Frick (and others) re design details of the Library. Includes poem for Miss Frick, "Vaunting the Vault; Tenor Ariette."
  - Frick, Henry Clay - Extracts from Will, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Furniture for Frick Art Reference Library - P.W. French, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Contains four original P.W. French watercolor drawings of tables and chair. Includes Clapp's criticism of the furniture design for the small Reading Room, the librarian's desk, and chairs, with drawings of his suggested changes.
  - Furniture for Frick Art Reference Library - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Contains drawings on tracing paper by Frederick Mortimer Clapp of suggested table for Catalogue Room, and two photographs of tables. Oversize drawings stored in Box C.
  - F - Miscellaneous, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Frick Residence - Contains drawing on tracing paper: Alt. - Frick Residence, Marc Eidlitz & Son and Heydt-Mugler Co. Inc. "Feuse" penciled on reverse side. Drawing stored in Box A.
  - Griggs, Maitland F. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Guaranty Trust Company of New York - Statements, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - G - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Giles, C. D. & Company
    Grilles - Re radiator covers.
    Grimson, Samuel B. [Electrical Research Products, Inc.]
  - Hammond, John Henry [The Frick Collection Counsel], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Topics discussed include tax exemption, salvage material acquired by Helen Clay Frick and Childs Frick, disposition of furnishings from guest rooms Nos. 1-4 (second floor) and guest room No. 1 on the third floor, and gift of furniture and porcelain in Mrs. Frick's Boudoir from Miss Frick.
  - Havemeyer, Horace [Trustee], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hines, Walker D. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Mr. Hines died on June 14, 1934. Folder contains memorial booklet printed by the New York City Bar Association and a handwritten copy of condolence note to Mrs. Hines.
  - Holmes Electric Protective Co., 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Holmes Electric Protective Co. - Contracts, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - House Committee, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - H - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Hale Desk Company
    Hayden Company
    Hoffman, Malvina - Re information on fountain for Frick Art Reference Library penthouse.
  - Insurance, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Inventories, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Inventory - Miscellaneous - Property Transferred to Collection (Mr. Naughton's Records), 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Re gifts of Helen Clay Frick, including works of art, furniture, drapery, flags, china, and rugs, listed by room location.
  - I - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Ingersoll-Rand Company
    Irving & Casson-A. H. Davenport Co. - Installed woodwork at Prides Crossing.
  - J - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Jarrett, Thomas M. [University of Pittsburgh Dept. of Fine Arts]
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Knoedler, M. & Co. [Thomas Gerrity] - Re inspection of paintings in vault for condition.
  - Lettering, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Re lettering style for The Frick Collection and Frick Art Reference Library signage. Includes samples.
  - Lettering - Photostats, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Thirteen oversize documents stored in Box C.
  - Lighting - Caldwell & Company Statements, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Contains lists and costs of all lighting fixtures in the Collection and Library.
  - Lighting - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Lee, Albert R., & Co. Inc. - Re lost and stolen art objects.
    Lockwood, Greene - Re air conditioning.
  - Marble, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Contains small blueprint of schedule of approved marble (Court Arcade, organ console, Oval Room). Also includes information on marble base in Court, famosa marble trim for door openings in the Reading Room, and marble selected for Library entrance stairs and Collection stairs.
  - Mellon, Andrew W. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Memoranda - F. M. Clapp and L. W. Eisinger [Clerk of the Works], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Re construction and design matters, including paint colors for the Library interiors.
  - Memoranda - F. M. Clapp and I. D. Matthew [Clerk of the Works], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Memoranda - F. M. Clapp and W. J. Naughton [Custodian], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Memoranda - L. W. Eisinger [Clerk of the Works] and W. J. Naughton [Custodian], 1934 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Memoranda - Rough Notes on Weekly Conferences, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Memoranda on Plans [2 folders], 1934 Jan.-May (Box 13, Folder 27-28)
  - Memoranda on Plans [3 folders], 1934 Jul.-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
    Contains reminders to discuss certain topics at upcoming meetings, short summaries of conversations, and miscellaneous notes both handwritten and typed. January 28, 1934 - Helen Clay Frick suggests using Malvina Hoffman's Shivering Girl as fountain on Frick Art Reference Library penthouse terrace.
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Clapp's Notes [4 folders], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
    Contains summaries of conversations, primarily with John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Helen Clay Frick, but also with Childs Frick, Maitland Griggs, Ethelwyn Manning, John Russell Pope, and John Henry Hammond. Topics discussed include the Widener house windows, air conditioning, the Library' lunette and terrace fountain, the cooling tower, a book conveyor annunciator, the organ, Library furniture, sidewalks, and the Library inscription.
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Eisinger's Notes [Clerk of the Works], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    L. W. Eisinger's notes on meetings with John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick Mortimer Clapp, and Helen Clay Frick. Also contains memos to Librarian Ethelwyn Manning. Topics discussed include a vacuum cleaning system, paneling for Ms. Manning's office, woodwork and other finishes in the Library, the organ, and sidewalks.
  - Memoranda on Plans - Mr. Matthew's Notes [Clerk of the Works], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Moorhead, William S. [Moorhead & Knox, Pittsburgh], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Re agreement between the Collection and the Library on sharing the cost of utilities.
  - Morgan, Junius S. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - M - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Magnanti, Angelo - Architectural decorator re Reading Room roundel molding.
    Matthew, I. D. [Clerk of the Works]
    McKey, Electa
    Miller-Druck Co., Inc. - Marble, mosaic, stone, and granite contractors.
    Morgan Library
    Murphy, Grayson M. P. - Re being disturbed by workmen at night.
  - New York Telephone Company, 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - N - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Naughton, W. J. [Custodian]
    New York Exchange for Woman's Work - Re $500 contribution Henry Clay Frick made in 1911.
  - O - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Otis Elevator Company - Contains text of press release re their contract with The Frick Collection.
    Overholt, Karl - Re value of Italian fireplace in Miss Frick's office for insurance purposes.
  - Pay Rolls [RESTRICTED FILE], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Photographic Departments [2 folders], 1934 (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    Contains correspondence with John Russell Pope re equipment and department layout. Also contains vendor brochures, and outside correspondence concerning sinks, dryers, and printers.
  - Plans, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Plans - Schedules of Room Numbers, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Contains list of assigned room numbers for the Collection and Library.
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] [2 folders], 1934 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    Contains many cursory notes referring to changes to be made in plans with approval granted. Most letters are from the firm, not John Russell Pope himself.
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] [16 folders], 1934 Feb.-Sep. (Box 15, Folder 1-16)
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] [6 folders], 1934 Aug.-Dec. (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Bids for Subcontract Work, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Contains signed tabulations of bids.
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Bills Paid, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Contract, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Drawings and Samples Submitted [4 folders], 1934 (Box 16, Folder 10-13)
    Contains forms that list drawings sent to the Collection or the Library, the name of shop, the number of copies, and remarks.
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Minutes of Weekly Conferences [2 folders], 1934 Jan.-Jun. (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
    Attendees may include: Frederick Mortimer Clapp, L. W. Eisinger, and I. D. Matthew (The Frick Collection); Daniel P. Higgins, Charles G. Anderson, and Mr. Ferrenz (office of the architect); Marc Eidlitz and Mr. Cotter (office of the builder); and Mr. Syska and Mr. Hennessey (engineers). Includes discussion of additions and deductions to budget, items pending action, and items approved and authorized, often with subcontractor's name and estimated cost.
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Minutes of Weekly Conferences [2 folders], 1934 Jul.-Dec. (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Pope, John Russell [architect] - Orders, 1932-1934 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pope, John Russell - Supplements Showing Changes to Plans, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Contains cover letters for revised plans sent to Mr. Clapp.
  - Printing, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Contains brochures from vendors.
  - Progress of Construction Work, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Painting of Library
    Park Association of New York City, Inc. - Membership pin stored in Box D.
    Planting - Re hedge.
    Plans - Includes index of plans for the Collection and Library.
    Pope, John Russell - Re "Rubens Vase."
    Powers Regulator Co.
    Pratt, H. L. [Standard Oil Company of New York]
  - Remington Rand Inc., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Repairs, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Report of Organizing Director, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Contains report for period of June 14, 1933 to March 28, 1934. Report summarizes construction progress, Garden Court excavation and shoring, schedules, air conditioning in vault, inventory, flood control, utility and other contracts, house account, 1934 budget and expenses, tax exemption, insurance, small catalogue, and watchmen.
  - Requests for Admission, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Majority of the requests were denied, except for Trenchard Cox, who viewed paintings in the vault; Philip Hendy of the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, who was shown the Bellini; and Chauncey B. Tinker, who was shown Gainsborough's The Mall in St. James's Park.
  - Requests for Information re The Frick Collection, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Requests for Permission to Reproduce Pictures in The Frick Collection, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Requests for Photographs of Articles in The Frick Collection, 1934-1935 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Rest Room No. 2 (Frick Art Reference Library Penthouse), 1934 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Oversize photostats of drawings stored in Box B.
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. [Trustee], 1934 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Roofing and Repairs - Committee on Organization and Policy, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Roofing and Repairs - Marc Eidlitz & Son and John Russell Pope, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Roofing and Repairs - Miscellaneous, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - R - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    RCA Victor Company, Inc. - Re talking picture equipment.
    Rose, Fred & Co. Inc.
  - Salvage Material - Eidlitz, Marc & Son, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Includes lists of items sent to Childs Frick and Helen Clay Frick with the amount they were charged, and "List of Porcelains from the Boucher Boudoir which Miss Frick has agreed to convey to the Collection."
  - Salvage Material - Miss Frick and Mr. Frick, 1934-1937 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Salvage items include furniture, ornamental railings, marble trim, mantelpieces, carved wood and canvas ceilings, plumbing fixtures, exterior ornamental stonework, woodwork, wrought iron fences and gates. Also includes list of porcelains from the Boucher Boudoir (Adelaide Frick's Sitting Room) which Helen Clay Frick has agreed to convey to the Collection. Eleven photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Salvage Material - John Henry Hammond [The Frick Collection Counsel], 1934 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Contains resolution regarding Helen Clay Frick and Childs Frick's payment agreement.
  - Salvage Material - Miscellaneous, 1932-1934 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Samples, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Contains bronze, leather and textiles samples for chairs, lights, doors, and hardware. Bronze hardware samples stored in Box D.
  - Schedules of Materials, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Shoring and Excavation - Marc Eidlitz & Son and John Russell Pope, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Includes report on shoring conditions, reasons for cost overruns, discrepancy in actual construction with Carrère & Hastings plans, and insurance.
  - Shoring and Excavation - Miscellaneous, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Six photographs of excavation transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Shoring and Excavation - Statements, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sidewalks, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Statements - Construction Account, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Statements - Construction Account - U.S. Trust. Co., 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Statements - Construction Connected Items, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Statements - Frick Collection House Account, 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Five oversize statements stored in Box A.
  - Statements - Miscellaneous, 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Syska & Hennessy [consulting engineers], 1934 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Includes January 26, 1934 four-page letter responding to questions about air conditioning posed by Childs Frick.
  - Syska & Hennessy [consulting engineers] - Bills, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Syska & Hennessy [consulting engineers] - Copies of Letters, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Contains copies of letters sent to John Russell Pope.
  - Syska & Hennessy [consulting engineers] - Fees, 1933-1934 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Sachs, Prof. Paul [Fogg Art Museum]
    Salvage
    Selby, Mr. [Wininger & Selby]
    Siple, Walter H. [Cincinnati Art Museum]
    Stamps
    Stoves
  - Tax Exemption Proceedings (Property), 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Taxes [RESTRICTED FILE], 1932-1935 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Temperature and Humidity Records, 1932-1934 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Contains graphs of house, vault and Fragonard Room relative humidity and temperature, and New York monthly and yearly relative humidity and temperature range.
  - Tile, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Trustees - Minutes of Meetings [RESTRICTED FILE], 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - T - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Telautograph Corporation
    Typing services
  - United States Trust Company, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - U - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    University of Pittsburgh - Re Odom Italian furniture.
  - Vault, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - V - Miscellaneous, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Van Wagoner-Linn Construction Co. - Re electrical work.
  - Watchmen Tour Service, 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Western Union, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Contains typed copies of telegram text.
  - Whitley, Frederic N., 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Contractor for Library fireplaces.
  - Widener Lattice, 1932-1934 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    George D. Widener, owner of Five East 70th Street, wanted the trellis work removed from the west side of his house. For architectural and legal reasons, the lattice was retained. Folder contains three photostats of lattice drawings. Oversize photostat of a drawing stored in Box B. Five photographs transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - W - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Walters Art Gallery
    Water Supply, Gas and Electricity, New York City Department of
    Watson, Mrs. Thomas E.
    Who's Who in America
    Wittenmeier Machinery Co. of New York [Freon supplier]
  - X-Y-Z - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    York Ice Machinery Corp. [Freon supplier]
- Central Files, 1935
  - Index, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Accounts, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Aeolian-Skinner Organ Company, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Contains list of rolls ordered for Concertola. Former rolls belonged to Helen Clay Frick and went to Pride's Crossing. Four photographs of organ (two close-ups of keys) transferred to The Frick Collection - Photographs; folder contains photocopies of photographs.
  - Air Conditioning, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Air Conditioning - Temperature Charts, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - American Association of Museums - Bulletins, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - American District Telegraph Company (Electric Protection Services), 1935 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Employment [3 folders] [RESTRICTED FILE], 1935 (Box 20, Folder 8-10)
  - A - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    American Art Annual
    American Association of Museums
    American Red Cross
    Angell, James Rowland [Yale Gallery of Fine Arts]
    Architects [registered in New York]
    Arden Studios, Inc.
  - Baker, George F. [Trustee], 1935 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Bludworth, Inc., 1935 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Information re electro-acoustical system for organ.
  - Bookstacks, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Brewer, H. K. and Company, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Stationery supplier.
  - Brooklyn Museums, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Buildings, Department of, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Contains Certificate of Occupancy for 10-12 East 71st Street.
  - By-Laws, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Contains draft By-Laws of December 23, 1935 and December 31, 1935, and comments and recommendations by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - B - Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Balay, Roland
    Balcom, H.G. [consulting engineer]
    Boston Museum of Fine Arts
    Bowser, S. F. & Company, Inc. - Re pumps and tanks.
    Brady, David
    Burroughs Adding Machine Company
  - Cabinet Work, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Contains memos and letters re the Collection main entrance doors, the Reception Hall ceiling, and Oval Room woodwork, as well as other areas of the Collection building. Includes memo on the reasons for color and finish changes in new walnut woodwork in the Collection. The Hayden Company was a subcontractor for the cabinet work.
  - Card Indices Room, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Re Library Card Catalogue Room. A mezzanine was added to the room.
  - Catalogue, Small - Porter Garnett, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Contract awarded to E.L. Hildreth & Company for The Frick Collection: Paintings: Summary Catalogue.
  - Catalogue, Small - E. L. Hildreth & Company, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Contains sample illustrations, samples of cloth for covers, dummies, and shipment records for The Frick Collection: Paintings: Summary Catalogue.
  - Catalogue, Small - E. L. Hildreth & Company - Proofs, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue, Small - Manuscript, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 2)